A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Richard Allison, Series 2 FA377
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller vice presidential records, Richard Allison, Series 2
1970-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Persico, Joseph E.
Allison, Richard
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
Howe, Jonathan Trumbull
United States. Office of the Vice President
FA377
51 document box(es)
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Biographical/Historical note
President Gerald R. Ford nominated Nelson A. Rockefeller to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon in August 1974. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 26 2
Arrangement note
This series is divided into 12 subseries:
Subseries 1 - Presidential Campaign 1976 Subseries 2 - Presidential Panel on Federal Compensation Subseries 3 - Domestic Council Subseries 4 - Energy Independence Authority (EIA) Subseries 5 - Establishment of Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) Subseries 6 - Science Advisory Groups for the Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) Subseries 7 - Administrative and Miscellaneous Files Subseries 8 - VIce Presidential Miscellaneous Files Subseries 9 - STATUS: Monthly Chartbook of Social and Economic Trends, Weekly Meeting with the President Subseries 10 - Chronological Files Subseries 11 - Miscellaneous Clippings Subseries 12 - Productivity Commission
Scope and Contents note
This series documents a portion of Nelson A. Rockefeller's public life from 1974 to 1977. Richard Allison was an assistant to Vice President Rockefeller, and these papers constitute background documentation for those files compiled in Record Group 26, Series 18: Working Papers of the Vice President.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Central Files (FA378)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, National Commission on Water Quality (FA379)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Press Releases (FA382)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Speeches (FA383)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
Political science; Presidential campaigns -- United States; International relations -- United States; National security -- United States; Prevention and health; Public health; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Social problems; Social sciences; Public policy; Social policy; Human rights; International economic relations; Federal government -- United States; Government policy; United States; Veterans -- United States; International relations; Technology; Economics; Education; Drug control; Economic policy; Environmental policy; Environmental sciences; Education -- United States; Energy; Water -- Purification; Water -- Pollution; Water conservation; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Persico, Joseph E.; Allison, Richard; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich); New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller); Howe, Jonathan Trumbull; United States. Office of the Vice President
- Presidential Campaign 1976, 1975-1976; 01; 2 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This subseries consists of correspondence and newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1976 Presidential election. The bulk of the material deals with the 1976 campaign strategy for President Gerald Ford. Notable figures in this subseries are Bob Dole, Jimmy Carter, Gerald Ford, Ronald Reagan, and Walter Mondale.
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, July-December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, January-April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, June 1-16, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, June 17-30, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, July 1-14, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, July 15-30, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, August 3-19, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Delegates and Alternatives for the Republican Convention, August 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Republican Convention Fact Sheets, August 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, August 20-31, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, September 2-13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, September 14-30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, October 1-19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, October 20-29, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Newspaper Clippings, November 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Convention Acceptance Speech Suggestions, July 14-August 2, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Convention Miscellany, July 22-August 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Ford Presidency: "A Portrait of the First Two Years", August 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - President Ford Issue Book, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Jimmy Carter Issue Book, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Meet The Press Background Material, August 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - National Press Club Background Material, October 26, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - National Press Club Background Material, October 26, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National Press Club Background Material, October 26, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - National Press Club - Drafts and Arrangements, October 26, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Platform Testimony - Background Material, August 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Presidential Panel on Federal Compensation, 1975-1975; 02; 1 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains memos, materials on meetings, and reports of the Presidential Panel on Federal Compensation, which was established by Presidential Memorandum to recommend appropriate levels of compensation for federal employees in accordance with the principle of comparability with nonfederal employee compensation. The panel was headed by Vice President Rockefeller from June 1975 to December 1975, and it was terminated upon submission of its final report on December 2, 1975.
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, May-July 1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, August 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, August 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings, August 6, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Final Report (Draft), August 1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, September 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, September 1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, October 1975 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Memos, Meetings, Reports, November 1975 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Memos, Meetings, Final Reports, December 1975 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Memos - Quadrennial Commission, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Domestic Council, 1970-1976; 03; 3.2 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of memos, background papers, activity reports, and policy reviews of the Domestic Council. The Domestic Council was formed in 1970 on the recommendation of the President's Advisory Council on Executive Organization. Developed as the domestic counterpart to the National Security Council, its major purpose was to create for the President a centralized, comprehensive policy-formulating group that would work closely with the relevant executive departments to analyze and develop policy initiatives on issues such as education, health care, welfare, drug abuse, veteran programs, civil rights, and natural resources.
  - General (I), May 4, 1970-February 12, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - General (I), February 14-March 20, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - General (II), March 25, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - General (II), March 25-April 30, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - General - Background Papers, April 1-30, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - General - Background Papers, May 1, 1975-March 11, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Activities Inventory, March 7, 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Activities Inventory, March 7, 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Needs/Policy Problems Study, March 20, 1975; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Needs/Policy Problems Study, March 20, 1975; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Needs/Policy Problems Study, March 20, 1975; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), July-August 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), August 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), September 1975 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), October 1975 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), November 3-20, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), November 21-30, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Public Forum - Denver, Colorado, October 21, 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Public Forum - Denver, Colorado, October 21, 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), December 10-16, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Policy Review and Forums (General), December 18, 1975-January 16, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Public Forum - Tampa, Florida, October 29, 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Public Forum - Tampa, Florida, October 29, 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Public Forum - Austin, Texas, November 11, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Public Forum - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 18, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Public Forum - Indianapolis, Indiana, November 25, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Public Forum - Los Angeles, California, December 9, 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Public Forum - Los Angeles, California, December 9, 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB)/Legislative Liaison Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Regulatory Matters, January-April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Regulatory Matters, May 1975 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Regulatory Matters, June-July 1975 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Regulatory Matters, August-October 1975 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Regulatory Matters, November-December 1975 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Regulatory Matters, January-March 1976 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Regulatory Matters, April-July 1976 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Proposal for a Committee on New York City, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Summer Jobs for Urban Youth, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Youth Employment/Jesse Jackson Projects, May-June 1976 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Youth Employment/Jesse Jackson Projects, June-October 1976 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Weekly (Periodic) Status Reports to the President, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Energy Independence Authority (EIA), 1974-1976; 04; 2.5 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of correspondence and information on meetings regarding the proposed Energy Independence Authority (EIA). President Gerald Ford submitted legislation proposing the establishment of the EIA on October 10, 1975. The proposal from President Ford was to establish an independent government-owned corporation, managed by a five-member board of directors, with authority to invest a total of $100 billion over a 7-year period in energy projects that would help the United States achieve energy independence. The EIA was to support projects in nuclear energy, solar energy, geothermal energy, and synthetic fuel technology. The legislation was never passed by Congress.
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, December 1974 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, January 1975 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, February 1975 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Report to Congress on the Economic Impact of Energy Actions, February 1975 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, March 1975 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, April 1-15, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, April 17-30, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, May 1-9, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, May 10-23, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, June 4-23, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, June 26, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, July 1-9, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, July 14-25, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, July 26-27, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, July 28-30, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, August 1975 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, September 1975 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, October 1975 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, November 1-10, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, November 13-25, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, December 2-10, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, December 15-22, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - National Energy Outlook, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, January 1976 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, February 1976 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, March 1976 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, April 1976 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, May 1976 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, July-August 1976 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Meetings, September-October 1976 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Labor Day EIA Speech - Drafts, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Vice President's Notes for Reader's Digest Article, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence, Related - Economic Growth in the Future, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence, Related - Kirkland and Meany, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence, Related - Hot Springs, Virginia, May 9, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence, Related - National Energy Policy Meeting, July 29, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence, Related - Industry Briefing - National Commission on Water Quality, September 10, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence, Related - Business Government Relations Council, October 6, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence, Related - Meeting with Bill Whyte, October 17, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence, Related - Chamber of Commerce, November 6, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 119)
- Establishment of Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP), 1975-1976; 05; 1.5 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of correspondence and information on meetings of the Office of Science and Technology Policy, which Congress established in 1976 with a broad mandate to advise the President and others within the Executive branch on the impact of science and technology on domestic and international affairs.
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, January 1975 (Box 21, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, February 1975 (Box 21, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, March-June 1975 (Box 21, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, July 1975 (Box 21, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, August 1975 (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, September 1975 (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, October 1975 (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, November 1975 (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, December 1975 (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, January 1976 (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, February 1976 (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, March 1976 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, April 1976 (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - Bill Prints, Drafts of, 1975-1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Bill Prints, Drafts of, 1975-1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 134)
  - Title III Committee, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 135)
  - Selection of Director, July 1975-March 1976 (Box 22, Folder 136)
  - Selection of Director, April 1976 (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - Selection of Director, May-August 1976 (Box 22, Folder 138)
- Science Advisory Groups for the Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP), 1975-1976; 06; 2 Cubic Feet
  Arrangement note
  This subseries is arranged chronologically.
  This subseries contains memos and information on meetings with the science advisory groups. Two science advisory groups were appointed by President Ford in November 1975. The first group, chaired by Dr. Simon Ramo, provided advice on the contributions of technology to economic strength. The other group, chaired by Dr. William Baker, provided advice on anticipated advances in science and technology. The groups' priorities were to set up a list of urgent scientific issues. The list included energy, food and nutrition, space, industrial productivity, health and safety regulations, and basic research.
  - General, June-July 1975 (Box 23, Folder 139)
  - General, July-September 1975 (Box 23, Folder 140)
  - General, September-October 1975 (Box 23, Folder 141)
  - General, November-December 1975 (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - General, December 1975-February 1976 (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - General, March-August 1976 (Box 23, Folder 144)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC, December 1-2, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC, January 14-15, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC - Supplemental, January 14-15, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 147)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC - Supplemental, January 14-15, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC, March 11-13, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 149)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC, March 11-13, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 150)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC - Supplemental, March 11-13, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 151)
  - Meetings - Moffett Field, California, April 22-23, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 152)
  - Meetings - Washington, DC, June 17-18, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 153)
  - Meetings - Los Angeles, California, August 5-6, 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 154)
  - Meetings - Los Angeles, California, August 5-6, 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 155)
  - National Science Foundation Directorship, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 156)
  - Nuclear Power (Political), September-December 1975 (Box 26, Folder 157)
  - Nuclear Power (Political), January-March 1976 (Box 26, Folder 158)
  - Nuclear Power (Political), April-August 1976 (Box 26, Folder 159)
  - Nuclear Power (Political), September 1976 (Box 26, Folder 160)
  - Nuclear Power (Political), October-November 1976 (Box 26, Folder 161)
  - Science and Technology - General, September-December 1975 (Box 27, Folder 162)
  - Science and Technology - General, January-April 1976 (Box 27, Folder 163)
  - Science and Technology - General, May-December 1976 (Box 27, Folder 164)
- Administrative and Miscellaneous Files, 1975-1977; 07; 3.6 Cubic Feet
  This subseries is arranged in the original folder order.
  This subseries consists of miscellaneous files, including vice presidential notes and clippings. It is likely that some of these documents are duplicated in other portions of the vice presidential papers.
  - Archives - Disposition of NAR Papers, May 1975-July 1976 (Box 27, Folder 165)
  - Archives - Disposition of NAR Papers, August 1976-January 1977 (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - Office Administrative Memos, January-December 1975 (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Office Administrative Memos, January-June 1976 (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Office Administrative Memos, July-August 1976 (Box 28, Folder 169)
  - Office Administrative Memos, September 1976-January 1977 (Box 28, Folder 170)
  - Office Procedures Memos, July-December 1975 (Box 28, Folder 171)
  - Office Procedures Memos, January-November 1976 (Box 28, Folder 172)
  - Presidential Assignments and Authorizations, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 173)
  - Thank-You Memos, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 174)
  - Personnel, 1975-1976
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted material
    - General, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 175)
    - A-M, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 176)
    - N-Z, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 177)
  - Transition - Vice President's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 178)
  - Albright Pension Fund Project, February 1975 (Box 29, Folder 179)
  - Albright Pension Fund Project, March 1975 (Box 29, Folder 180)
  - Bicentennial - General, January-May 1975 (Box 29, Folder 181)
  - Bicentennial - General, September 1975-January 1976 (Box 29, Folder 182)
  - Bicentennial - Herman Kahn Project, August 1974-May 1975 (Box 29, Folder 183)
  - Bicentennial - Herman Kahn Project, June-August 1975 (Box 29, Folder 184)
  - Bicentennial - Herman Kahn Project, September 1975-May 1976 (Box 30, Folder 185)
  - Bicentennial Speech Project, July-October 1975 (Box 30, Folder 186)
  - Bicentennial Speech Project, November 1975-February 1976 (Box 30, Folder 187)
  - "Future of Freedom" Speech Project, January 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 188)
  - "Future of Freedom" Speech Project, January 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 30, Folder 189)
  - "Future of Freedom" Speech Project, February 1976 (Box 30, Folder 190)
  - "Future of Freedom" Speech Project, March 1976 (Box 30, Folder 191)
  - "Future of Freedom" Speech Project, April-August 1976 (Box 31, Folder 192)
  - "Future of Freedom" Copies of Releases, February-May 1976 (Box 31, Folder 193)
  - Defense of Freedom - Draft, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 194)
  - NAR - Handwritten Outline (Box 31, Folder 195)
  - William Ronan - Foreign Policy for Americans, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 196)
  - Oscar Ruebhausen - The United States in a Changing World, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 197)
  - Nancy K[issinger] Draft, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 198)
  - NAR - Election Year Foreign Policy Debates and Political Distortions, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 199)
  - Ronald Reagan's Television Address - NBC Network, March 1976 (Box 31, Folder 200)
  - Jon Howe Quotes - Angola (Box 31, Folder 201)
  - Jon Howe - Defense of Freedom Outline, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 202)
  - Jon Howe - DVN Memo (Vietnam), April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 203)
  - Jon Howe - Memo - Panama, April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 204)
  - 1972 National Press Club Speech (Box 31, Folder 205)
  - Ronald Reagan Facts (Box 31, Folder 206)
  - Ronald Reagan Television Spot, April 28, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 207)
  - Stockpiles [oil], April 1976 (Box 31, Folder 208)
  - Vice President Draft, April 30, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 209)
  - U.S. Budget and HR 5247 Bill, February 1976 (Box 31, Folder 210)
  - Correspondence from Ted Braun, March 1975-August 1976 (Box 31, Folder 211)
  - Correspondence from Mike Deutch, November 1974-December 1975 (Box 32, Folder 212)
  - Correspondence from Edward Teller, May 1975-April 1976 (Box 32, Folder 213)
  - Critical Choices Commission, January 1975-July 1976 (Box 32, Folder 214)